Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Press Releases
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, press releases
1992-2009
RU 370
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
5.75
The materials consist of Yale press releases.
Yale University. Office of Public Affairs
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-C (YRG 4-C), Records documenting public information functions of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Existence and Location of Originals
Press releases sent to the Archives prior to 1992 are classed in the Yale Publications Collection (Y91 +A2).
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of Yale press releases.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged chronologically.
Universities and colleges -- Public relations; Press releases; Yale University -- Public relations; Yale University. Office of Public Affairs
- Press releases, Series I
  - 1992 Jul - 1993 Jun (Box 1)
  - 1993 Jul -1994 Jun (Box 2)
  - 1994 Jul -1995 Jun (Box 3)
  - 1995 Jul -1996 Jun (Box 4)
  - 1996 Jul -1997 Jun (Box 5)
  - 1997 Jul -1998 Jun (Box 6)
  - 1998 Jul- 2000 Feb (Box 7)
  - 2000 Mar - 2001 Dec (Box 8)
  - 2002-2003 (Box 9)
  - 2004-2005 (Box 10)
  - 2006-2007 (Box 11)
- Additional Material, Accession 2019-A-0022
  - 2008 Jan - 2009 Mar, Accession 2019-A-0022 (Box 1)